I am a man between two trees. It's
time again for a man between two
trees.
Once again, once again ladies and
gentlemen, it's that time. Gather
the clan up.
Not that kind of clan. So, so so so
so so so so What's cool is I can
record
like this. Just clip it on and
there we go. A little green thing
will be caught up
into there. Yeah, whatever. So
here's a freeform riff on my
birthday. As that Basement Jack
song says so well, "Where's your
head at, at, at? Where's your head
at?
Where's your head at?" I'll put the
link below. I got a song for
literally every angle of life.
So today is it, motherfucker. It's
graduation day. It's graduation day
from the old Burt,
all the old shit, all the old
stories, all the old framing of
things. Always,
let me calm myself down. I have to
be very clear with my words. Not
always, but
referencing the past in a negative
way that actually continues to
perpetuate
negative frequency in my life. And
the timer's going off because this
means
I should stop video at this point.
Should I let go? Sounds like I'm
sitting in the yard playing music
for myself. Oh, here goes the
repeating.
I should probably go up there. So
yeah, there are more to say. I'll
say more in a little bit.
I can say this, that I do feel that
for people that have gone through a
long period of trauma,
CPTSD, all kinds of nasty stuff,
and you know what? No doctor, no
therapist, no
special magic person is going to
show up and tap you on the shoulder
and look you in the eye and
say, "You're done. It's all over."
So I believe it's incumbent upon
oneself when you feel
as though the inside of you is
ready, but the outside world isn't
yet. That's when you declare
you're done with the old shit. And
I believe that by declaring that,
and I believe,
I believe by declaring that, you
put frequency out into the
universe. You need to speak these
things literally out loud so that
your voice creates sound waves,
right? Isn't that the idea
that a butterfly on one side of the
world creates a typhoon on the
other side? So little things have
a big impact. And I know this from
COVID times. Every single day, I
was in the deepest of my
depression and my mind consistently
was focused on negativity, the bad
things. I was constantly
thinking about the things I did not
want to come true. And ultimately,
those were the things. Come on,
sucker. Thank you, motherfucker.
Maybe there's a new Casper site
tonight. I had this boom. Wait,
you're telling me we weren't
recording?